<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>pmslava</title>
    <link>https://www.pmslava.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on pmslava</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.pmslava.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How to set up a static website with Hugo, GitHub Pages and Namecheap as a domain registrar</title>
      <link>https://www.pmslava.com/posts/how-to-set-up-a-static-website-with-hugo-github-pages-and-namecheap-as-a-domain-registrar/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.pmslava.com/posts/how-to-set-up-a-static-website-with-hugo-github-pages-and-namecheap-as-a-domain-registrar/</guid>
      <description>Hi there! This is my first post on this site and I think it&amp;rsquo;s a nice tradition to start it from the explanation on how this site was setted up.
Why a static website Link to heading In short the combination of these gives you a very simple, fast and reliable personal blog:
Hugo - for generation a static website GitHub Pages - for hosting your static website Namecheap - for buying the domain name of your site Additionally it worth mentioning that the costs of this setup is that your domain name will cost, Hugo and GitHub Pages are free for small blogers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://www.pmslava.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.pmslava.com/about/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;PM&amp;rdquo; is a special acronym for me. The letter P reflects three main areas of experience for me: Product, Project, and Process. The letter M stands for Manager, which is my main profession.
My name is Slava, and I can:
create products, manage projects, analyze processes, and provide trainings. In all these four areas, I have results that I am not ashamed of. You can find examples of my work on the Projects page of my website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://www.pmslava.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.pmslava.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>Hello and thank you for visiting my personal website!
If you&amp;rsquo;re looking to connect with like-minded individuals, or if you have any questions or comments about my website, I&amp;rsquo;d love to hear from you. As someone who values meaningful connections, I&amp;rsquo;m always happy to connect with good people.
Feel free to drop me a message at mail@pmslava.com and I&amp;rsquo;ll do my best to respond as soon as possible.
Thank you for visiting my website, and I look forward to hearing from you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://www.pmslava.com/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.pmslava.com/projects/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my projects page. Here, you will find a collection of some of my most significant and successful projects. These projects reflect my expertise, creativity, and commitment to delivering exceptional results to my clients and collaborators. I invite you to explore this page and discover the unique and innovative solutions I have developed. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re looking for inspiration or considering working with me, I hope that my portfolio will showcase the quality and value of my work.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
