<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on &gt;&gt;</title>
    <link>https://www.pmslava.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on &gt;&gt;</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://www.pmslava.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Top 55 Useful AI Tools</title>
      <link>https://www.pmslava.com/posts/top-55-useful-ai-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.pmslava.com/posts/top-55-useful-ai-tools/</guid>
      <description>The list of useful AI tools is inspired by the Howfinity video &amp;ldquo;I Tried 1200 AI Tools - These Are the Top 50&amp;rdquo;.&#xA;1. Jasper AI by OpenAI Link to heading Jasper AI, a pioneer in generative AI for content creation, assists in crafting marketing content with the backing of GPT technology from OpenAI.&#xA;Category: Content Creation and Writing Assistance. Strengths: Intuitive content generation. Weaknesses: May require user edits for precision.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Skill Map for a Software Product Owner</title>
      <link>https://www.pmslava.com/posts/skill-map-for-software-product-owner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.pmslava.com/posts/skill-map-for-software-product-owner/</guid>
      <description>In an ever-changing world of software development, the role of a product owner is constantly evolving, blending a mix of technical knowledge and strategic insight. As the tech landscape shifts, so do the skills required to be effective in this role. This article offers a skill map, thoughtfully designed for both established and aspiring software product owners. It outlines key areas of expertise necessary in today&amp;rsquo;s market, including development, emerging technologies, marketing, sales, product management, and project management.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to set up a static website with Hugo, GitHub Pages and Namecheap as a domain registrar</title>
      <link>https://www.pmslava.com/posts/how-to-set-up-a-static-website-with-hugo-github-pages-and-namecheap/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.pmslava.com/posts/how-to-set-up-a-static-website-with-hugo-github-pages-and-namecheap/</guid>
      <description>Hi there! This is my first post on this site and I think it&amp;rsquo;s a nice tradition to start it from the explanation on how this site was setted up.&#xA;Why a static website Link to heading In short the combination of these gives you a very simple, fast and reliable personal blog:&#xA;Hugo - for generation a static website GitHub Pages - for hosting your static website Namecheap - for buying the domain name of your site Additionally it worth mentioning that the costs of this setup is that your domain name will cost, Hugo and GitHub Pages are free for small blogers.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
